[{"answer": "Is there a problem", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Right", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Boy, that's fucking genius.  You're a fucking genius.  Then you're just sitting there, bullshitting with me. Man, no way I coulda done that", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Holy shit!  my friend wants to know my name", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Took a guess.  Lucky for you, I guessed right", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I work for the government", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "This is something that is never going to end.  You can never work in the business again with this contract, because he will find you. To survive, you have to go into deep hiding.  And that's going to take money, a lot of money", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "If you walk out that door, my friend will still come after you", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Listen", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Where you wanted to be", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "How did you get into the business", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Because I want to know", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Are they usually like that", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "They become complicated... messy", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Did it ever bother my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "It.  Tell it.  For all I know it could be a machine", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Sorry", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "The beach?  It was nice", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You'll be here.  A restaurant.  A public place far enough away that he won't notice you, but with a good enough view you'll be able to see him when he moves inside", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Then, we wait", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What is it?  I don't like this at all.  What is going on here", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't believe that", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No.  I went back to the hotel.  And waited", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes.  Here I am again", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Isn't it interesting though?  I mean, look at us, in this room.  Or yesterday, when we were walking in the plaza market.  I mean, we look like just another couple.  But what are we?  Doesn't it seem so crazy", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I didn't want to complicate the situation", "docId": "Assassins.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "It can be", "qsentId": 30}]